HARRIET AMORKOR OKAI







okaiharriet88@gmail.com https://amokor.github.io/my portfolio/index.html

UI/UX designer with 3 years of experience creating streamlined and intuitive controls. Dedicated to creating inviting and unintimidating interfaces for users and consistently employing the understanding of user psychology throughout design process.

EDUCATION

2014 - 2018

Ghana Communication University College

BSc. Human Resource Management

SKILLS

User Research Communication Collaboration Wireframing Design Thinking Usability Testing

Prototyping Adobe XD HTML

Sketch (Maze Notion Dovetail

CERTIFICATIONS

September 2022

Memorisely

User Research Credential ID 002045

August 2022

Interaction Design Foundation (IxDF)

Mobile User Experience Design Credential ID 114182-2022-664196

July 2022

Interaction Design Foundation (IxDF)

Human Computer Interaction Credential ID 114182-2022-718022

WORK EXPERIENCE

2020-Present

Walulel (UI/UX Designer)

- Designing and developing visually appealing and user-friendly interfaces for web and mobile applications.
- Conducting user research and usability tests to inform design decisions and ensure optimal user experience
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams, including developers, product managers, and marketing teams
- Contributed to the development of a design system, improving design consistency and efficiency.
- Managed design projects from conception to launch, ensuring designs met business goals and user needs

May 2022- July 2022

Terralix (Freelance - UI Design)

 Incorporated modern aesthetics through sketching, wireframing and prototyping

Oct 2020-Dec 2020

Walulel

Web Development Intern (Backend)

- Creation of resources (database migrations, models, controllers to get info from database, returning information)
- Testing and documentation of APIs
- Creation of a Todolist API (CRUD function)
- Documented project changes in team manuals for future reference and use.